[{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":9347,"timeElapsed":43549},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3557,"timeElapsed":47113},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":50076},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9684,"timeElapsed":59765},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7055,"timeElapsed":66826},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4907,"timeElapsed":71738},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":5920,"timeElapsed":77664},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664414261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5124,"timeElapsed":82794},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664418305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":86838},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664428564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8605,"timeElapsed":97097},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3093,"timeElapsed":100195},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664434790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3123,"timeElapsed":103323},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5490,"timeElapsed":108819},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2394,"timeElapsed":111218},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3956,"timeElapsed":115179},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664448861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2210,"timeElapsed":117393},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4823,"timeElapsed":122221},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664458968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5275,"timeElapsed":127501},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664467908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7490,"timeElapsed":136441},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664473337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5423,"timeElapsed":141869},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5657,"timeElapsed":147531},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664484557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5554,"timeElapsed":153090},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664487039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":155571},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664489154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":157687},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664493617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4458,"timeElapsed":162150},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664496714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3092,"timeElapsed":165247},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664499526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2808,"timeElapsed":168059},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664506321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5344,"timeElapsed":174854},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664509285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2959,"timeElapsed":177817},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664512065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2776,"timeElapsed":180598},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664516360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4290,"timeElapsed":184893},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2411,"timeElapsed":187308},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664522972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4191,"timeElapsed":191504},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664526019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3043,"timeElapsed":194552},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531963,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5939,"timeElapsed":200496},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664535990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4022,"timeElapsed":204523},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664540821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4826,"timeElapsed":209354},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664547563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5090,"timeElapsed":216096},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664554390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6822,"timeElapsed":222922},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664559137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4743,"timeElapsed":227669},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664565647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6506,"timeElapsed":234180},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2709,"timeElapsed":236894},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664570959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2593,"timeElapsed":239492},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664574054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3091,"timeElapsed":242587},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664576468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2409,"timeElapsed":245001},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664580365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3893,"timeElapsed":248898},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664587592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5740,"timeElapsed":256124},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664590822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3226,"timeElapsed":259355},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664594985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4157,"timeElapsed":263517},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664599464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4474,"timeElapsed":267997},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664602311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":270843},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664605624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3309,"timeElapsed":274157},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664608288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2659,"timeElapsed":276821},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664617046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8753,"timeElapsed":285578},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664620775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3724,"timeElapsed":289308},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664628868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5824,"timeElapsed":297401},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664632581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3708,"timeElapsed":301114},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664635226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":303759},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664640989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5757,"timeElapsed":309522},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664643703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2710,"timeElapsed":312236},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664648616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4908,"timeElapsed":317149},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664652145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":320678},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664654127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1977,"timeElapsed":322660},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664656789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2657,"timeElapsed":325322},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4543,"timeElapsed":331567},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664665813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2774,"timeElapsed":334346},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664668129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":336662},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664671907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3773,"timeElapsed":340440},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664678602,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6690,"timeElapsed":347135},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664681516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2910,"timeElapsed":350049},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664684064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":352597},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664686427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2358,"timeElapsed":354960},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664689193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2762,"timeElapsed":357726},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664691322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2124,"timeElapsed":359855},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664698000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5374,"timeElapsed":366533},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664701814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3809,"timeElapsed":370347},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664705275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3456,"timeElapsed":373808},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664709322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4042,"timeElapsed":377855},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664714234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4908,"timeElapsed":382767},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664716815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2576,"timeElapsed":385348},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664719529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2708,"timeElapsed":388061},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664722943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3409,"timeElapsed":391476},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664727204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4257,"timeElapsed":395737},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664736812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7703,"timeElapsed":405344},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664740442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3626,"timeElapsed":408974},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664744605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4159,"timeElapsed":413138},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664749083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4473,"timeElapsed":417616},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664753096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4009,"timeElapsed":421629},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2660,"timeElapsed":424294},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664758157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":426690},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664761256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3094,"timeElapsed":429788},{"subjectID":"1tg926f7ba","prolificID":"6148b49d6ac652cefd310332","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214da86014dda643c1f3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664763836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2576,"timeElapsed":432369}]